const questions = [  
    { question: "1.) How do you write 'Hello World' in an alert box?",    
      options: ["A.) msgBox('Hello World')", "B.) alertBox('Hello World')", "C.) alert('Hello World')", "D.) msg('Hello World')"],
      answer: "2"
    },
    {
      question: "2.) Inside which HTML element do we put the JavaScript?",
      options: ["A.) script tag", "B.) javascript tag", "C.) js tag", "D.) scripting tag"],
      answer: "0"
    },
    {
      question: "3.) How do you create a function in JavaScript?",
      options: ["A.) function(myFunction)()", "B.) function = myFunction()", "C.) function:myFunction()", "D.) function myFunction()"],
      answer: "3"
    },
    {
      question: "4.) How do you call a function named 'myFunction'?",
      options: ["A.) call myFunction()", "B.) call function myFunction()", "C.) myFunction()", "D.) myFunction(function)"],
      answer: "2"
    },
    {
      question: "5.) Which event occurs when the user clicks on an HTML element?",
      options: ["A.) onmouseover", "B.) onclick", "C.) onchange", "D.) onmouseclick"],
      answer: "1"
    },
    {
      question: "6.) How to write an IF statement in JavaScript?",
      options: ["A.) if (i == 5)", "B.) if i = 5", "C.) if i == 5 then", "D.) if i = 5 then"],
      answer: "0"
    },
    {
      question: "7.) How to write an IF statement for executing some code if 'i' is NOT equal to 5?",
      options: ["A.) if (i <> 5)", "B.) if i =! 5 then", "C.) if i <> 5", "D.) if (i != 5)"],
      answer: "3"
    },
    {
      question: "8.) How does a FOR loop start?",
      options: ["A.) for (i = 0; i <= 5; i++)", "B.) for i = 1 to 5", "C.) for (i <= 5; i++)", "D.) for (i = 0; i <= 5)"],
      answer: "0"
    },
    {
      question: "9.) How can you add a comment in a JavaScript?",
      options: ["A.) !--This is a comment--", "B.) 'This is a comment", "C.) This is a comment\\", "D.) //This is a comment"],
      answer: "3"
    },
    {
      question: "10.) How to insert a comment that has more than one line?",
      options: ["A.) !--This comment has more than one line--", "B.) /*This comment has more than one line*/", "C.) /This comment has more than one line/", "D.) \\This comment has more than one line\\"],
      answer: "1"
    }
  ];

  export default questions;
  
